# Introduction

A professional Senior full stack developer with sufficient experience on design & develop the large-scale web-based application. I enjoys being part of a successful and productive team. A thinker, writer, and craftsman. I spent 70% of my time in front end and 30% of my time in backend.

The most challenging front end project to me is KingMed Digital pathology program which is developed with react&redux to handle over billions of case each year. In this project we face a lot of performance challenging and we do lot of optimization to make it fast, secure and efficient.

The most challenging backend project which I done is bidflows which we combine 2 kind of real time tech(web socket and webrtc) to make virtual streaming auction feasible, scalable and convenient. We also adopt the secure&reliable multi-tenancy implementation in Nestjs since it is a SAAS product.

The most famous I do in day to day life is okibook which allows you book tables at good price in advance which the most challenging part is the limited developing time while having complex domain logic in inventory rule which is developed in a correct and quick way with our TDD approach.

Specialty: react, redux, front end optimization, node js, Program design, TDD, JS, Nest Js, Cloud

# Personal Information

Name: Chung Chi Fu Gender: Male Birth: 1991-1 Contact No: +852 67348649 Email:

chungchi300@hotmail.com Notice Period: 1 month

# **Top 3 Projects&Products**

#### **Bidflows**

Bidflows is a platform that has

- Real-time Live/Online Auction
- Multi-language
- Customizable Product
- Drag and drop page builder(react)
- video/image medias(cloudinary)

#### Software Development

- Design&Implement Restful API using nest js that implement Multi-tenancy(One database for one client). Auto documented by swagger
- Payment Integration with Stripe for order payment.
- Payment Integration/Monthly subscription with Zoho subscription/ Zoho Book
- Front End(React&Redux, Websocket for real time communication)
- Integration with opentok for live streaming

- Sharing library in front end by multi package between the admin panel and user panel
- Batch Image Upload
- Batch Product/Lot Import
- Drag and drop page builder

#### Legal document & Cooperation

- Hire and manage with a remote designer on upwork
- Prepare legal documents for SAAS service contract.
- Prepare legal document for partnership
- Monthly subscription payment by ZOHO(support ACH)

### KingMed Diagnostics - digital pathology program

KingMed Diagnostics - digital pathology program (Front end) - KingMed Diagnostics is the largest independent diagnostic laboratory and pathology service provider in China. KingMed Diagnostics raised a round of funding on September 08, 2017.

#### Front End

- Select and apply React&Redux to create Digital Pathology Web Application to handle > 1,000 annotations. The client uses the program to handle >10 million cases per year.
- Styling by styled.component(Post CSS)
- Create, export, and reuse the front-end library(using Browserify and Rollup) that can be reused in the Digital pathology system and Artificial intelligence training of Digital pathology system.
- Discuss the user flow and program behavior with client and designer to achieve user to have the highest efficiency to complete a similar task in the industry.
- API Design(A RESTFUL API in JSON format, use jwt-token as identity information)
- Design the network layer/logic so that the application can work smoothly in poor network conditions.
- Resource evaluation for different project and task, also teach other programmers to use react&redux, end to end API test
- Solve the compatibility issue to allow front end program can be used in Modern Browser(IE11,Chrome,Firefox).
- Solve Common Network threat(e.g xss and crsf by cookie header)
- Teaching and cooperate junior developer

#### Okibook

Fully responsible for the design and implementation work for

#### Backend development

- Laravel
- Authentication
- Image Upload
- Batch Import Discount

#### Front end development

- Bootstrap
- Autocomplete
- Discount design
- · Admin Panel for multiple restaurant owner

# Work Experience

#### Rsc Tech Partner LLC - Co founder

Dates Employed: Mar 2020 - Present

#### Software Development

- Develop real-time bidding and video streaming SAAS auction platform http://bidflows.com/.
- Hire and manage with a remote designer on upwork
- Front End & Back End Development

#### Legal document & Cooperation

- Prepare legal documents for SAAS service contract.
- Prepare legal document for partnership
- Monthly subscription payment by ZOHO(support ACH)

### Madison Auction Limited - IT Specialist

Dates Employed: Oct 2018 - Feb 2020

#### Software Development

- Develop real-time bidding and video streaming for O2O online/offline auction platform https://bid.mfwauction.com/ in a short period of time when service provider stops to provide related service using nodejs(typescript) and reactjs which significantly increases operational efficiency and customer satisfaction.
- Develop wine estimator
- Develop Chinese version auction platform which deployed to Aliyun to serve China Customer smoothly.
- Improve software development cycle by integrated bug reporting tool and JIRA.

#### Empower company by cooperating with a different system

- Procure and manage an online and live-streaming auction platform. Develop 3rd parties report plugin which allows providing customer experience and back-office efficiency.
- Procure and manage CRM in order to provide better customer service. Get about 40% discount by custom negotiation.
- Procure and manage knowledge management system for IT knowledge.
- Cooperate with the digital marketing company.

#### Operation

Arrange the first live-streaming and the first online-only auction which has total sales 2500W.

### Astri - Software engineer

Dates Employed: May 2016 - Sep 2018

#### Software Development

#### **King Med**

- Design and Develop Digital Pathology Diagnosis Web Application KingMed Diagnostics the largest third-party medical laboratory group in China which win Smart Living(Smart Healthcare)
  Silver Award of ICT Award 2019
- Select and apply React&Redux to create Digital Pathology Web Application to handle > 1,000 annotations. The client uses the program to handle >10 million cases per year.
- Create, export and reuse the front-end library(using Browserify and Rollup) that can be reused in Digital pathology system and Artifical intelligence training of Digital pathology system.
- Discuss the user flow and program behavior with client and designer to achieve user to have the highest efficiency to complete a similar task in the industry.
- API Design(A RESTFUL API in JSON format, use jwt-token as identity information)
- Design the network layer/logic so that the application can work smoothly in poor network condition.
- Resource evaluation for different project and task, also teach other programmers to use react&redux, end to end API test
- Solve the compatibility issue to allow front end program can be used in Modern Browser(IE11,Chrome,Firefox).

#### www.abshare.com online advertising platform

- Front end development by react & redux
- API design
- Mobile, desktop compatibility issue

### Aigens - Software engineer

Dates Employed: Nov 2014 - Feb 2016

#### Software Development

Design and implement different E-Commerce System with Complex Flow

# Hong Kong Famous 5 star Restaurant Online Booking Platform(>70 restaurants) with best price guarantee - www.okibook.com

- Use laravel to develop MVC web application ,to implement 3 different permission, operation & interface for client, restaurant owner and the website admin.
- Adopt TDD and Unit test approach to implement the application in a very short period of time.
- Integrated and deployed AWS ElasticBeanstalk as hosting server.

#### Hong Kong Largest online wine p2p selling platform - www.vy.com.hk

- Use laravel to develop MVC web application & javascript to support complex b2b order&order fulfilment flow
- Integrate and implement the Elastic Search to support complex search of over 80,000 wine in a second
- Integrated and deployed AWS ElasticBeanstalk as hosting server.
- Integrated mailgun to support massive email delivery and report.

# Education

The Open University of Hong Kong

Degree Name: Bachelor's DegreeField Of StudyComputer ScienceGrade (First class honours)

Dates attended or expected graduation: 2011 – 2014

Activities and Societies: Wing Chun Society

# **Next Job Expectation:**

As a developer, want to do deeper or wider

Go Deeper-> super complex front end application, react & redux

Go Wider->back end application,nodejs & java(j2ee)

(scalable & extreme & more extreme performance tuning)

Domain:

e-commerce, auction, financial, medical, crypto

Reputation: Big Company or Corporate

Title: SA, Senior Software Engineer

Preference: Big Company in Shenzhen Mid-size: insurance, virtual bank in HK, insurance in hk

# Salary

my last job salary: 30000 hkd/month, 1 month guarantee bonus

30000hkd \* 13 = 390K / year work from home 60% of my time Good food and wine

expected salary:

520K / year

# **About Me**

My Blogs: https://jeff-chung.com/ Github: https://github.com/chungchi300 Leetcode: https://leetcode.com/chungchi300/

# Availability

Immediate Available